

24 December 1991 in Sfax



Street Habib Bourguiba, 3001 Sfax, Tunisia



ahmedrgueii@gmail.com



+216 22 99 13 43



Driving license B

## Languages

Arab Native

French Bilingual proficiency

English Professional working

proficiency

Spanish Elementary

proficiency

# Associative way

Responsible « Club Culturel Ali Belhouane » CCAB Sfax.

Former vice president : « Club des Futurs Informaticiens » FSEGS.

Member: « Sfax Mezyena ».

# AHMED RGUEI WEB DEVELOPER <? phip?>

# Master in Computer Science

#### About me

I'm a web developer living in Sfax, Tunisia. Currently, I spend my days to be more and more professional in the world of web development to be one day an expert. From back end programming (Native PHP, CakePHP, Symfony2) to front end engineering (HTML, CSS, bootstrap, and JS/JQuery) my experience grow with happiness and passion. Also, my dream is to be involved in big projects and make innovative ones.

#### Education

2013 – 2015 FSEG Sfax	Master in Computer Science, SINT « Software			
	engineering », 13.10 / 20.			
2010 – 2013 FSEG Sfax	Licence in Computer Science, IT applied to			
	management, 14,40 / 20.			
June 2010 H.S. Hadi Shaker	Bachelor of science.			

# Experiences

06/2016 – Today	Web	develope	r (front	end,	back	end	
MC-Dev Sfax	progra	amming):	HTML5,	CSS3,	Boots	strap,	
	JS/JQuery, AJAX, PHP5, POO.						
06/2014 - 09/2014	Commercial store manager: HR and IT manager.						
Sicom+ Sfax							
02/2013 - 09/2013	Project graduation: Web application, Computer						
MTD Group	Assisted Production Management « GPAO »						

HTML5, CSS3, JS, CakePHP.

### Skills

#### Programing skills

HTML5 CSS3 \*\*\* Bootstrap \*\*\* JavaScript \*\*\* **JQuery** \*\*\*\* Ajax \*\*\* PHP5 \*\*\* CakePHP Symfony2 Service Web \*\*\* SOL Java **AspectJ** C/C#.NET

#### Conceptual skills

UML \*\*\*\*\*\*\*\*
Merise \*\*\*\*\*
POO \*\*\*\*\*\*
MVC \*\*\*\*\*\*

#### Other skills

Cloud Computing

Big Data

Database Administration

Data Mining

Data Warehouse

#### Research

**RCIS 2016** One of the authors of the article « Developing a Cloud selection system for business processes », Publication published in the conference RCIS 2016. Research project Master 2: « Outsourcing 02/2015 02/2016 business processes: design and realization of a Laboratory recommendation system of Cloud provider ». MIRACI February 5, 2016, obtained with 16 / 20. Keywords: Web Service, Cloud Computing, recommendation system, genetic algorithm, AHP.

# Volunteering Experience

- Participation in intercultural exchange (Tunisia, France, Germany): 6 12 march 2016 in Dunkerque, France. *Object*: Refugees: how to help and integrate them into our society, Sustainable Development. *Organisations*: CCAB Sfax, OFAJ/DFJW.
- Participation in intercultural exchange (Tunisia, France, Germany): 1 6 December 2016 in Bonn, Germany. *Object*: Fair trade: opportunities and how to persist the economic development, Sustainable Development. *Organisations*: CCAB Sfax, OFAJ/DFJW.
- Attendance to the 4th International Web Service Symposium WSS'2014: December 27-28, 2014 Sfax, Tunisia.
- Participation in the annual « Coding Party V2.0 » December 25-26, 2015, ISIMS Microsoft Club.
- Organizer of cultural events in Sfax (International Festival of Sfax 2013 and 2014, International Festival of Music Sfax 2015 ...).

#### Interests

Sports: Football, Athletics. Music: Classic, R&B, Pop.

Reading: Novels and Fictions. Voluntary work

in/ahmed-rguei-567703b4

f /ahmedrgueii

(ahmed.rguei